Guide to the Lionel Barrow Papers, 1940-2008 RL.00084
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Personal Files, 4
  - Snapshots, 1951, 1953, 1976, 1981-1983; 1 boxes (Box 20)
  - Snapshots, 1983-1985; 1 boxes (Box 21)
  - Snapshots, 1985-1988; 1 boxes (Box 22)
  - Snapshots, 1988-1992, 1995; 0.5 boxes (Box 23)
  - Snapshots, 2005 (Box 23)
  - Snapshots, undated; 3 folders (Box 23)
  - France snapshots, undated (Box 23)
  - WABJ conference photographs, 1984 (Box 23)
  - NABJ conference photographs, 1983-1984 (Box 23)
  - Photographs (large), 1946, 1989, 2008, undated (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous photograph albums, undated (Box 23)
  - ID card album, undated (Box 23)
  - Snapshots, unsorted, 1980s (Box 25)
  - Snapshots and snapshot albums, unsorted, 1980s (Box 26)
  - Snapshot albums, unsorted, 1980s (Box 27)
  - Chairborne Infantry essays, by Barrow, 1951 (Box 19)
    re: 24th Infantry in Korea
  - Is there a future for Blacks in Business Communications?, 1977; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - untitled chapter draft: "Relative Potency - Theory", undated (Box 19)
  - Toward a Code of Ethics in the Newsroom drafts, etc., 1977-1981 (Box 19)
  - Preparing for the Search, 1984 (Box 19)
  - The Minorities and Communication Division: The Beginning, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Eliminating Racism in Religious Communications, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Women Wear Clothing, Why?, undated (Box 19)
  - Oakland Terrace School: What Martin Luther King Means to Me, 1990 (Box 19)
  - The We Nobody Knows: Minority Children and Television position paper, 1974 (Box 19)
  - A Dream Deferred: testimony for the Black Congressional Caucus, 1972; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Untitled Butler University speech re: Dream Deferred to high school students, 1989 (Box 19)
  - The Morehouse Man: A Myth or Legend in his Time, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Alexander Hamilton High School, Brooklyn: high school commencement address, 1968 (Box 19)
  - New Uses of Covariance Analysis, 1967 (Box 19)
    Published in Journal of Advertising Research.
  - A Minority View of the Media, 1982 (Box 19)
  - The Community News: History and Purpose, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Communication in the 80s: Change or More of the Same, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Black Regiment's Flag Raised After 44 Years, 1995 (Box 19)
  - The Negro Consumer: The Fast Reappearing Indian, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Bruce Westley: The Behavioral Sciences and Communication Education, 1985 (Box 19)
- Writings and Speeches, 4
- Audiovisual Materials, 5
  - 27 audiocassettes in 2 boxes (Box 19)
  - 2 VHS tapes from COE (Box 19)
- Wilhelmina Barrow Materials, 1940s-1970s; 6
  - American Red Cross, 1940s; 1
    - Red Cross publications and booklets, 1940s (Box 28)
    - Magazines: Overseas Woman, 1945 (Box 28)
    - Program reports-Army Rest Centers, 1946 (Box 28)
    - Wilhelmina Barrows official documents, 1945-1947 (Box 28)
    - Club training-reference materials, 1945-1947 (Box 28)
    - Post-war transport newspapers, The Crow's Nest, 1946 (Box 28)
    - Returning soldier information, 1945-1946 (Box 28)
    - At Your Service publications, 1946 (Box 28)
    - Yank and other army-related publications, 1945-1946 (Box 28)
    - Airline pamphlets and souvenirs, 1940s (Box 28)
    - Italy guides and postcards, 1940s; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - France guides and postcards, 1940s; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - French speaking guides, 1940s (Box 28)
    - Other guides and postcards, 1940s (Box 28)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1940s (Box 28)
  - International and UN materials, 1940s-1960s; 2
    - Wilhelmina Barrow UN publications and other materials, 1950s-1960s (Box 28)
    - Clippings, international news and United Nations coverage, 1940s-1960s (Box 28)
  - National Council of Negro Women (NCNW), 1950s; 3
    - National Council of Negro Women materials, 1950s-1960s (Box 29)
    - NCNW Resolutions, booklets, 1953-1954 (Box 29)
    - NCNW Report, 1953-1957 (Box 29)
    - NCNW newspaper clippings, 1954 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, 1940s-1970s; 4
    - Morehouse College mailings, 1960s (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1940s-1970s; 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Wilhelmina Barrow's printed materials, 1950s-1960s (Box 29)
      Books for Graduate Nurses, 1950; Paris Travel Guide; My Appeal to the British, Mahatma Gandhi; Directory of Members of the American Sociological Society, 1956; American Overseas Association, 1964; Post-War Plan, Rutherford Wright